<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Licensing.Defaults xmlns="http://alphacentaury.org/Licensing.Data/v1" appliesTo="InternalTools">
  <Libraries>
    <License>Ms-RL</License>
    <Authors>Codeplex/GitHub user AlphaCentaury</Authors>
    <Copyright>Copyright (C) 2014-2019, Codeplex/GitHub user AlphaCentaury and its contributors</Copyright>
    <Product>Internal tools for IPTViewr</Product>
    <TermsAndConditions format="MD"><![CDATA[
This COMPONENT (“SOFWARE”), either in binary or source code form, is **licensed under the terms of the _Microsoft Reciprocal License (Ms-RL)_** except for “THIRD-PARTY” components.  \
All other rights are reserved by the author(s) of the software.

_**THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED “AS IS”, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND**_, express or implied, including but not limited to the warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement.  \
In no event shall the authors or the copyright holders be liable for any claim, damages or other liability, whether in action of contract, tort or otherwise, arising from, out of or in connection with the software or the use or other dealings in the software.

All trademarks, service marks, trade names, product names and logos are the property of their respective owners.  \
Its use in the context of this product does not constitute endorsement nor support by their respective owners.
]]></TermsAndConditions>
    <TermsAndConditions format="MD" language="ES"><![CDATA[
Este COMPONENTE (el “SOFTWARE”), ya sea en forma de código binario o fuente, está **sujeto a los términos de la Licencia Recíproca de Microsoft _“Microsoft Reciprocal License” (Ms-RL)_**, excepto en lo relativo a componentes de terceras partes (“THIRD-PARTY”).  \
Todos los demás derechos están reservados por el/los autor(es) del software.

**EL SOFTWARE SE PROPORCIONA “TAL CUAL”, SIN GARANTÍA DE NINGÚN TIPO**, expresa o implícita, incluyendo (pero no limitándose a) las garantías de comerciabilidad, idoneidad para un propósito particular y no infracción.  \
En ningún caso, los autores o titulares del Copyright serán responsables de ninguna reclamación, daños o cualquier otra responsabilidad, ya sea en una acción de contrato, agravio o cualquier otro motivo, con o sin relación con el software o el uso u otros aspectos del software.

Todas las marcas comerciales, marcas de servicio, nombres comerciales, nombres de productos y logotipos son propiedad de sus respectivos propietarios.  \
Su uso en el contexto de este software no constituye un respaldo ni apoyo por parte de sus respectivos propietarios.
]]></TermsAndConditions>
  </Libraries>
  <Programs>
    <License>Ms-RL</License>
    <Authors>Codeplex/GitHub user AlphaCentaury</Authors>
    <Copyright>Copyright (C) 2014-2019, Codeplex/GitHub user AlphaCentaury and its contributors</Copyright>
    <Product>Internal tools for IPTViewr</Product>
    <TermsAndConditions format="MD"><![CDATA[
This PROGRAM (“SOFWARE”), either in binary or source code form, is **licensed under the terms of the _Microsoft Reciprocal License (Ms-RL)_** except for “THIRD-PARTY” components.  \
All other rights are reserved by the author(s) of the software.

_**THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED “AS IS”, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND**_, express or implied, including but not limited to the warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement.  \
In no event shall the authors or the copyright holders be liable for any claim, damages or other liability, whether in action of contract, tort or otherwise, arising from, out of or in connection with the software or the use or other dealings in the software.

All trademarks, service marks, trade names, product names and logos are the property of their respective owners, including, in some instances, Grupo Telefónica.  \
Its use in the context of this product does not constitute endorsement nor support by their respective owners.

Logos of movistar+ channels might be provided with this software. These logos are the property of the respective channels and businesses.  \
Logos are provided in “good faith”, in order to identify the different channels and no copyright infringement is intended.
]]></TermsAndConditions>
    <TermsAndConditions format="MD" language="ES"><![CDATA[
Este PROGRAMA (el “SOFTWARE”), ya sea en forma de código binario o fuente, está **sujeto a los términos de la Licencia Recíproca de Microsoft _“Microsoft Reciprocal License” (Ms-RL)_**, excepto en lo relativo a componentes de terceras partes (“THIRD-PARTY”).  \
Todos los demás derechos están reservados por el/los autor(es) del software.

**EL SOFTWARE SE PROPORCIONA “TAL CUAL”, SIN GARANTÍA DE NINGÚN TIPO**, expresa o implícita, incluyendo (pero no limitándose a) las garantías de comerciabilidad, idoneidad para un propósito particular y no infracción.  \
En ningún caso, los autores o titulares del Copyright serán responsables de ninguna reclamación, daños o cualquier otra responsabilidad, ya sea en una acción de contrato, agravio o cualquier otro motivo, con o sin relación con el software o el uso u otros aspectos del software.

Todas las marcas comerciales, marcas de servicio, nombres comerciales, nombres de productos y logotipos son propiedad de sus respectivos propietarios, incluyendo, en su caso, al Grupo Teléfonica.  \
Su uso en el contexto de este software no constituye un respaldo ni apoyo por parte de sus respectivos propietarios.

Los logotipos de los canales de movistar+ pueden estar incluídos con el software. Estos logotipos son propiedad de los diferentes canales y sus compañías propietarias.  \
Los logos se suministran de “buena fe”, para poder identificar adecuadamente los diferentes canales, sin ánimo de infringir ningún derecho de copyright.
]]></TermsAndConditions>
  </Programs>
  <Licenses>
    <License id="Ms-RL" name="Microsoft Reciprocal License (Ms-RL)" format="MD" />
  </Licenses>
</Licensing.Defaults>